I didn't even know about government before.
I had no idea, but it wasn't until I was sitting in that room and I saw the power.
Like I saw who was making the laws, like they're making bills every every day.
Wait, can I just tell you this?
I don't think people really understand that these people are making laws.
Yeah.
Like I think people really because I will tell you somehow that thread has been like disconnected for folks because they're just like, oh, it's a politician.
They are lawmakers.
Yes.
I don't even want to call them politicians anymore.
I've been calling people lawmakers because I'm like, y'all need to understand that these mofos will take a pen and change your life that quick.